The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Who would like to buy this artifact ?
The City Lord's mansion is hiring a steward. Want to try ?
250 low quality spirit stones and not one more !
Don't try to scam me !
The other shop
offered 300.
Don't be ungrateful !
It's just a ginseng !
In our Teng Family City...
Shut up !
That's a thousand years old blood ginseng
worth at least 1 000 spirit stones !
Little Brother,
come back ! We can negotiate !
At least 1 000 ?
I've never seen so many spirit stones in my life.
Let alone that Wang Lin kid.
Once I manage to sell this,
I bet he'll be shocked.
Hurry, let's go !
What do you want !?
Fighting is forbidden here !
Flying is forbidden in Teng Family City.
Didn't you know that ?
Who...
Are you the one that killed Bai Zhan ?
Thankfully, I reacted fast.
You're too slow.
So it was just an ambush to lure me here ?
How stupid of me
to only realize this now...
You're not worth all the trouble I went through to trap you.
Who are you !?
The one who'll kill you.
Is this sword a Core Formation artifact now ?
Of course,
a top-quality Core Formation artifact.
But you must be careful,
Blood Refining binds your life to this artifact.
If the sword is damaged,
you'll suffer a severe backlash.
What brings you here ?
Scram !
Excuse me...
Chase him !
Why are so many Teng Family disciples chasing me ?
You go this way,
I'll go that way.
Okay !
Wait,
something's wrong.
There's a flight suppression formation...
The gate is the other way.
Zhang Hu is still in the market...
Why is there no one here ?
No, it's not right.
Something's wrong,
I must quickly find Zhang Hu.
Late stage Foundation Establishment !
Smart people are troublesome,
I need to catch you myself.
Be careful !
Were you looking for your friend ?
Zhang...
Zhang Hu !
There is no grudge between us,
why are you so cruel ?
I was entrusted with this task
so I had to do it.
Is this Old Man Ji Mo's doing ?
Sorry...
Don't worry,
you'll meet him again soon.
You actually have a top quality Core Formation artifact ?
That little sword will be mine !
If you were Foundation Establishment,
we could've dueled.
It's a pity you're just a Qi Condensation brat.
Movement speed\Ntalisman
You're dead !
So only the Teng Family can fly here !
That bastard
is clearly just playing with his prey.
He's got some good items.
This kid is getting interesting.
Shit,
my movement speed talisman is ending !
In Teng Family City,
even Core Formation cultivators can't escape me,
let alone you !
Go !
It looks like these lanterns
are the secret of Teng Family City's formation.
You dare to break our formation !?
Ancestor,
the young master can't handle this guy.
Junior fears he might lose this fight.
What cultivation does Li'er's target have ?
Ancestor, he is Qi Condensation.
And what is Li'er's cultivation ?
The young master is at Late stage Foundation Establishment.
Li'er lacks mental fortitude.
If this fight can temper him,
repairing this city
is a small price to pay.
Thunder talisman
Little ant,
being killed by my divine sword
is an honor !
This is bad !
He also has a teleportation artifact ?
That one will also be mine !
That sword is a Nascent Soul artifact,
I had to teleport you.
Senior, are you alright ?
I'm hanging on.
You're dead !
A defensive mirror ?
He also has a Nascent Soul defensive artifact !?
Damn it, he's doing it again !
Let's see how many times you can teleport !
3 days later
I'm out of spirit liquid,
I need to get some more.
Little Lin, my Origin Soul's power is fading
I can only teleport you a few more times.
Hold on Senior !
Misty Forest
This forest is strange...
He's catching up.
500 li to the south is the Misty Forest.
Note: 1 li = 500m
The forest is shrouded in a fog
that blocks Divine Sense.
It's also filled with deadly beasts.
But the worst of all
are the Blue Thread Vines.
Don't enter it before Core Formation.
I have a Nascent Soul artifact,
what can this forest do to me ?
Even that Qi Condensation brat dared to enter it.
Why should I be afraid of it ?
I will kill him today !
Blue Thread Vines !
Little Lin, stop !
Stop !
You must resist your instincts
and avoid fighting it with spiritual energy !
These vines drain spiritual energy
and are extremely sensitive to blood.
If you fight back, they will tighten their grip
until they consume you.
Fighting them head on
is suicide.
I will get you out of here while I can still
do some teleports.
I won't run away.
If you offend me once,
I will accept it.
But if you offend me a second time
I'll exterminate you !
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?